<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on GESS RNG Biogas</title><link>https://gessrngbiogas.com/</link><description>Recent content in Home on GESS RNG Biogas</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 23:19:26 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gessrngbiogas.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Contact Us</title><link>https://gessrngbiogas.com/contact-us/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 16:22:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://gessrngbiogas.com/contact-us/</guid><description>Contacts Cody Lee Manure &amp;amp; Digestate Specialist cody.lee@gessrng.com
Shaun Lee Managing Partner shaun.lee@gessint.com
Nicholas Vassilakis Environmental Engineer nico.vassilakis@gessrng.com
Tony Pinckney Project Manager tony.pinckney@gessrng.com
Addresses Mailing Address 9920 Kincey Ave. Suite 120Huntersville, NC 28078</description></item><item><title>Why GESS RNG Biogas</title><link>https://gessrngbiogas.com/why-gess/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 16:20:37 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://gessrngbiogas.com/why-gess/</guid><description>We strive to achieve global renewable energy goals while excelling in providing state-of-the-art waste management solutions. GESS RNG Biogas works towards establishing a better future especially with the ravaging of our global climatic conditions. We utilize agricultural wastes from dairy and swine farms, and food wastes converting them to carbon-neutral renewable natural gas (RNG). This RNG produced - is an extremely versatile bio-energy source and fully compatible considering the existing U.</description></item><item><title>Careers</title><link>https://gessrngbiogas.com/about-us/careers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 16:16:12 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://gessrngbiogas.com/about-us/careers/</guid><description>If you’re a bright individual who is passionate about improving the environment and making a positive impact, then click the button to join our team! Join Our Team</description></item><item><title>Partners</title><link>https://gessrngbiogas.com/about-us/partners/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 16:15:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://gessrngbiogas.com/about-us/partners/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Our Team</title><link>https://gessrngbiogas.com/about-us/team/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 16:13:01 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://gessrngbiogas.com/about-us/team/</guid><description> Our diverse team of engineers, business professionals, and biogas experts is committed to protecting the planet and creating a cleaner environment for future generations.
We are passionate about developing sustainable and reliable fuel sources and providing innovative waste solutions to agricultural producers across the United States.</description></item><item><title>Food Processing Waste Profits</title><link>https://gessrngbiogas.com/industries/food-processing-waste/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 15:16:49 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://gessrngbiogas.com/industries/food-processing-waste/</guid><description>GESS RNG Biogas will transform your waste into profit through sustainable technology solutions. We offer complete environment solutions for your food processing waste operation. Click below to have a free site assessment completed by GESS RNG Biogas for your operation.</description></item><item><title>Dairy Profits</title><link>https://gessrngbiogas.com/industries/dairy-waste/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 14:47:38 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://gessrngbiogas.com/industries/dairy-waste/</guid><description>Sand costs a lot of money for bedding, and so does the cost of hauling it out mixed with manure.
The GESS RNG Biogas team will transform your waste into profit through sustainable technology solutions. We offer complete environment solutions to solve your sand and manure problem and turn it into profits. Click below to contact us to have our project development team complete a free site assessment of your operations.</description></item><item><title>Swine Profits</title><link>https://gessrngbiogas.com/industries/swine-waste/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 14:47:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://gessrngbiogas.com/industries/swine-waste/</guid><description>GESS RNG Biogas will transform your waste into profit through sustainable technology solutions. We offer complete environment solutions to collect and remove biosolids from your swine slurry production. Click below to have a free site assessment completed by GESS RNG Biogas for your property.</description></item></channel></rss>